CHICAGO,ILLINOIS
伊利诺斯州 芝加哥
Here,Gremlin.
在这里 捣蛋鬼
Yeah. We'll fly up in October.
是的 我们10月份飞过去
That would be great. Yeah.
那样就太好了 是的
Hey,mom,you wanna talk to Charlie?
嘿 妈妈 你想跟Charlie说话吗?
Charlie. Hello. Charlie,say hi to grandma.
Charlie 嘿 Charlie 跟外婆问好
No. Okay,I'm sorry,mom. She's zoned out.
不想说 好吧 抱歉 妈妈 她看电视出神了
I know. We've cut back.
我知道 我们已经削减开支了
Mom,the kids are great.
妈妈 孩子们都很好
Hey,you're home early.
嘿 你回来真早
Mom,call you back.
妈妈 回头再打给你
You okay?
你还好吗?
We need more water. Fill the sinks and tubs.
我们需要更多水 把水槽和浴缸装满水
We don't have much time.
我们没多少时间了
Ben,stop.
Ben 等等
It's happening,isn't it?
快要发生了 是吗?
Bass,why don't you just call her?
Bass 你为什么不直接打电话给她?
Call her? Nobody calls anybody any more.
打电话给她? 现在没人打电话了
Come on,man. She's 22. She doesn't even talk on the phone.
拜托 老兄 她22岁 她根本不聊电话
What,you wanna give me some tech advice,huh?
怎么 你想给我点技术性建议么?
You with your big fat Casio '80s brick phone.
用你那只80年代的卡西欧砖头大哥大么
Yeah.  It's my brother.
是的 我哥打来的
- Benjamin,what's up? - Where have you been?
- Benjamin 怎么了? - 你去哪儿了?
What's going on? What's the matter?
出什么事了? 怎么了?
I've been calling. Where are you?
我一直在打你电话 你在哪里?
She's sending photos.
她在发照片
We,uh,went out,had a few. We're on our way back to base.
我们出去喝了点酒 正在回基地的路上
What's going on? What's wrong?
出什么事了? 怎么了?
Listen to me very,very carefully.
你仔细听好了
- Look at that. - Shh,shh,shh.
- 快看 - 嘘
- It's all gonna turn off. - What?
- 一切将会关闭 - 什么?
It's gonna turn off,and it will never,ever turn back on.
一切将会关闭 再也不会打开了
What's gonna turn off? What are you talking about?
什么会关闭? 你在说什么?
Everything. Everything's gonna turn off.
一切 所有一切都会关闭
Ben? Did I lose you?
Ben? 没信号了吗?
No,no,no.
不 不 不
Miles.
Miles
What the hell is going on?
到底出什么事了?
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET- ÑÅ±´
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 小力水手 黑米 茶泡饭 Sleeper ts 校对: 尉迟逸 时间轴: 雅贝
REVOLUTION Season 1 Episode 1
末世革命 第一季 第1集
15 YEARS AFTER THE BLACKOUT
全球失去电力15年后
What you gotta understand is things used to be different.
你要明白 过去的一切与现在不同
We used electricity for everything,for our computers,our phones,
过去我们做什么事都需要电 比如电脑 手机
even to grow food and pump water.
甚至种植庄稼 泵取水源
But after the blackout,nothing worked.
但电力消失后 一切都无法使用
Not even car engines or jet turbines.
汽车引擎和飞机发动机都不例外
Hell,even batteries. All of it gone forever.
甚至电池 一切从此消失
People starved. Sickness without medicine. Fires without fire trucks.
人们食不果腹 疾病无药可医 连发生火灾也没有消防车灭火
Governments fell. Militias rose up.
政府垮台 军权崛起
If you were smart,you left the city.
聪明的人会离开城市
If you weren't,you died there.
否则只能葬身于此
So what the hell happened? What caused the blackout?
到底发生了什么呢? 是什么使电力消失了呢?
So what does everybody think?
大家都有什么看法?
I know that learning isn't as cool as bow hunting or whatever,
我知道学习并非像射箭打猎之类的有趣
but still,this should bother you.
但你们应该想一想
Physics went insane. The world went insane overnight,and nobody knows why.
物理现象完全乱套 全世界 一夜之间陷入混乱 但没人知道原因
Hey,Ben!
嘿 Ben!
Hey. Morning,Caleb.
嘿 Caleb 早上好
Morning,Ben.
早上好 Ben
- Morning,Aaron. - Hey,Ben.
- 早上好 Aaron - 嘿 Ben
You look terrible.
你脸色真难看
I was up all night.
我一夜没睡
Had a menage-a-raccoon in my backyard.
后院有只浣熊吵了一晚上
Hmm?
来点儿吗?
Seen Charlie and Danny?
看到Charlie和Danny了吗?
They left early. They said they were going hunting.
他们很早就走了 说是去打猎
Better be.
最好是这样
Take a look.
过来看看
Charlie,how 'bout we actually go hunting for once?
Charlie 我们能真正去打一次猎吗?
No one's stopping you.
又没人拦你
Really?
真的吗?
The freezer,it doesn't work. It's all gonna melt anyway.
冰箱不能用了 反正也会化的
Whoa,slow down,kiddo.
吃慢点 孩子
I want you to really,really remember what it tastes like,okay?
我要你好好记住这个味道 好吗?
Danny?
Danny?
I'm fine,okay?
我没事 好吗?
You're not fine. You're having an asthma attack.
怎么没事 你哮喘发作了
I can't breathe!
我不能呼吸了!
All right,now suck this back. Doctor's orders.
好了 喝了这个 这是医嘱
Maggie,this is awful.
Maggie 这真恶心
Yes,it's for the asthma.
是的 但这是治哮喘的良药
You were supposed to watch out for him.
你本该照顾好他的
I'm sorry.
对不起
You know that road's not safe.
你知道那条路不安全
I know. I'm sorry,really.
我知道 我真的很抱歉
It's just--
只是...
Go on.
说吧
Nothing's safe. Everything is off-limits.
没有一个地方是安全的 哪儿都不能去
I am just trying to look out for you.
我只是想保护你
I don't need you to. I mean,dad,if it was up to you,
我不需要 我是说 爸爸 如果一切你说了算的话
you wouldn't even let us leave our street.
你甚至都不会让我们离开这条街
Fine,you know what,then wander off into the the wild blue.
好吧 那你逛到荒山野岭中
Get your throat slit by bandits or get yourself lynched by a Militia.
被强盗割断喉咙 被军权团私刑处死
Does any of that sound good to you?
难道这样才好吗?
It's not all like that.
不是这样的
I don't know,it can get pretty rough out there.
说不准 外面的世界太凶险
There's other towns like ours,right? Other people?
还有像我们一样的城镇 住着其他人 对吧?
Trust me. There is nothing worth seeing,not any more.
相信我 没什么值得看的
Look,I was your age once. I get it.
听着 我也经历过你这个年纪 我懂的
But he's right. Things are--
但他说得对 世界...
Excuse me,is she a part of this family now?
抱歉 她现在是我们的家人吗?
Is that what's going on here?
是这样吗?
She hops into bed with you,and,what,that makes her mom?
她跟你上床 于是就成了我妈?
No! Your mom is gone. She died out there.
不! 你妈妈去世了 她死了
You wanna end up just like her?
你想要跟她一样的结局吗?
I'm sorry. Charlie,I didn't--
对不起 Charlie 我不想...
Here we have some mint. Look at this.
这些是薄荷 你看
What we're gonna do is we're gonna rub it between our fingers like this.
我们用手指摩擦它 像这样
Okay,honey,I need you to go with your mom now.
亲爱的 去你妈妈那
All right,y'all,come on. Come on.
大家过来 过来
- Take it. Take it. - No--
- 拿着 拿着 - 不
Don't let anybody know that you have it.
别让任何人知道你有这个东西
If anything happens to me,just do what I told you.
如果我出什么事了 就按我说的做
Stay off the road,they're gonna be looking for it.
远离马路 他们会找这个东西的
Keep it safe. Do you understand?
保护好它 明白吗?
Ben,nothing is gonna happen to--
Ben 你不会有事的...
Aaron,please.
Aaron 求你了
My God. What a beautiful village.
天哪 多漂亮的村庄
This must be a mistake. We already paid our spring taxes.
肯定有什么误会 我们交过春天的税了
Oh,it's not about your crops.
这和你们的作物无关
We're not here with the local garrison.
我们不是当地卫戍部队
Do you know a Ben Matheson?
你认识Ben Matheson吗?
You're looking at him. What's this about?
正是我 有什么事吗?
Miles Matheson. He's your brother?
Miles Matheson是你的弟弟吗?
That's right.
是的
Where is Miles?
Miles在哪里?
I haven't seen him in years. What's this about?
我好几年没见过他了 他怎么了?
I'm here under the orders of General Sebastian Monroe himself.
我奉Sebastian Monroe将军之命而来
He personally asked me to find two men.
他让我找到两个男人
You... and your brother.
你... 和你弟弟
Hold on just a second.
慢着
I'm gonna have to ask you to come with us under the authority of the Monroe Republic.
根据Monroe共和区的规定 你得跟我们走一趟
Why?
为什么?
Do I have to repeat myself?
我还得再重复一遍吗?
I just don't understand.
我只是不太明白
Here's what you need to understand.
你需要明白的是
I have been searching for you for a very long time through mud and filth,
我一路跋涉找了你很久
away from my home and my wife and my bed.
背井离乡 无法与妻子团聚
So I'm in a mood.
所以我心情不太好
I'm sure you can understand that.
相信你可以理解我的
So do yourself a favor and climb in that wagon,
所以 麻烦你自己爬上马车
or so help me,I will conscript all of your children,
不然我把你的孩子都征入军队
and I will reeducate them until they no longer remember your names.
重新改造他们 直到忘记你
Are we clear?
明白了吗?
May I have a moment?
能稍等一下吗?
Maggie,I'm gonna go with them.
Maggie 我要跟他们走了
No,you can't go.
不 你不能走
I need you to look after my kids.
你帮我照顾孩子们
- No. - It's gonna be okay.
- 不 - 不会有事的
- No,you won't come back. - Maggie,it's okay.
- 不 你回不来的 - Maggie 不会有事的
Ben,no,it's not going to be okay.
Ben 不 你会出事的
You can't take him.
你们不能带他走
Danny,stop.
Danny 住手
I suppose this is your boy?
这是你儿子吧?
My dad,he didn't do anything.
我父亲没做错什么
Danny,put it down.
Danny 放下
We don't want any trouble. Just go,please.
我们不想惹上麻烦 请你们走吧
- Easy now. - Danny,look at me.
- 别激动 - Danny 看着我
Tell him to put his gun down.
叫他把枪放下
Put his gun--tell him to put his gun down!
把枪... 叫他把枪放下!
Danny,I said put it down.
Danny 我说了 把弩放下
Kid's got a point,Ben!
孩子说得有道理 Ben!
How 'bout they put theirs down?
为什么他们不能把枪放下?
Sir,owning a firearm is a hanging offense.
先生 持有火器可是死罪
So go hang yourself.
那你去死吧
- Caleb. - Think about it.
- Caleb - 认真考虑
I swear to God,I'll shoot him.
我对上帝发誓 我会杀了他
Put it down.
把弩放下
Can you just leave us alone? Please,just go. Just forget about it.
你不能放过我们吗? 求你们走吧 忘了这事
- Danny,listen to me. - Put it down!
- Danny 听我说 - 把弩放下!
- Tell him to stop. - You need to do what they say.
- 让他住手 - 你得按他们说的做
- Put it down! - Stop,stop.
- 快放下! - 住手 住手
Back up!
退后!
Ben!
Ben!
Enough.
够了
- Come here. - Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
- 过来 - 爸爸! 爸爸!
- Please,no! No! No! - Dad!
- 求你们了 不! 不! 不! - 爸爸!
Danny!
Danny!
Dad!
爸爸!
Dad.
爸爸
What happened? What--what happened?
出什么事了? 出什么事了?
Danny's gone.
Danny被抓走了
Danny's gone? Who--
Danny被抓走了? 谁...
Militia. Militia took him.
军权团 军权团的人把他抓走了
Okay,okay,what do we do? What do you want me to do?
我们得怎么办? 你想我怎么做?
Listen,my brother Miles is in Chicago.
听着 我弟弟Miles在芝加哥
At the Grand on Walton Place,Miles is there.
在Walton大酒店 Miles就在那里
He can get Danny. You need to find Miles.
他可以把Danny救回来 你得找到Miles
Dad,no. No,we'll catch the soldiers.
不 爸爸 我们可以去追那些士兵
We can go right now. We'll take him back.
我们现在就可以去 我们会把他救回来
No,no,they'll kill you.
不 不 他们会杀了你的
But you're gonna come with me.
但你得跟我一起去
Okay? You're gonna come with me.
好吗? 你要跟我一起去
- I can't. - Yes,you can. Please,please.
- 我不行 - 你可以的 求你了 求你了
Listen to me,Charlie.
听我说 Charlie
You're strong. You're so strong. You're like your mom.
你很坚强 你像你妈妈一般坚强
You can do this. You have to do this.
你可以做到的 你一定要完成这件事
At least wait till tomorrow. You need to sleep.
至少等到明天再出发吧 你需要休息
I'm wasting time.
我已经在浪费时间了
This doesn't make any sense. Why would they take Danny?
没道理 为什么他们要带走Danny?
I don't know. I guess we'll know when we find him.
我不知道 我们找到他之后就能知道了
Maggie,that's,uh... that's really nice of you,
Maggie 你真好
but they need you here.
但他们需要你留在这
James can take over as town doctor.
James可以接手成为这里的医生
I'll be fine.
我不会有事的
Maybe so,but I'm still coming with you.
或许是的 但我还是要跟你一起去
You don't seem to understand.
看来你不明白
I don't want you to come.
我不想你跟我一起去
And I don't think you understand. I'm not doing this for you.
我想你也不明白 我这么做不是为了你
You have got to be kidding me.
开什么玩笑
Uh,your dad was my friend. I am going too.
你父亲是我的朋友 我也要去
Aaron,I mean,come on,you're afraid of bees.
Aaron 拜托 你害怕蜜蜂
I'm not afraid of bees. I am allergic to bees. There is a big difference.
我不害怕蜜蜂 我对蜜蜂过敏 区别大着呢
Well,it's your funeral.
好吧 你这是自寻死路
Probably,yes.
或许是的
Son,I'm sorry you're mixed up in all this.
孩子 抱歉把你牵扯进来
But you gotta understand,
但你得明白
if I couldn't have your dad,I had to take you.
如果我不能抓你父亲回去 我不得不带你回去
Couldn't go back empty-handed.
不能空手回去
But make no mistake. It's a mess.
但别再添乱了 已经一团糟了
Bad news for everyone.
对每个人而言都不是好消息
Go.
快去
To tell you the truth,when general Monroe finds out,
说实话 等到Monroe将军发现真相
he's gonna be irate.
他绝对会怒不可遏
Might even have my head.
可能会杀了我
Let's hope.
希望如此
Let's not forget,you drew first.
别忘了是你先挑起事端的
That puts your daddy's blood on your hands,son.
是你害死了你父亲 孩子
Hi,boy. How's my good boy?
我的马还好吗?
Yeah,you want food? Good boy.
想吃东西吗? 马儿
You know,a walk like this,I counted on sore,
像这样的长途跋涉 我知道会很疼
but not on the,you know,chafing issues.
但我没想到会擦伤发炎
So this brother,Miles,what do we know about him?
关于这个Miles 我们了解多少?
How do we know that he can help us?
我们怎么知道他能帮我们?
All my dad ever said about him was that he's good at killing.
我父亲只告诉我他擅长杀戮
Oh. That's comforting.
这话听着挺欣慰的
You know,most people just say good morning.
多数人会打声招呼
I was,um--
我...
Good morning.
早上好
'Morning. I'm Nate.
早上好 我叫Nate
Charlie.
我叫Charlie
Where were you headed,Charlie?
你要去哪 Charlie?
None of your business,Nate.
不关你的事 Nate
That's true.
这倒是的
I'm gonna get some water.
我要去取点水
Where have you been?
你去哪了?
Just getting some water.
取水
Aaron,maybe we should camp somewhere else.
Aaron 也许我们应该在别处扎营
No,come on. They usually hide a doctor's kit up front. Good meds.
快来 他们通常会把医药箱 藏在飞机前舱 里面都是好药
How do you know?
你怎么知道的?
I,uh,owned one,a plane.
我曾经有过一架飞机
Seriously?
真的?
Yeah. I used to work at this place called Google.
是的 我曾经在谷歌工作
That was a computer thing,right?
是个电脑公司吧?
Now...it's nothing.
现在... 什么都不是了
$80 million in the bank,
我会立刻用银行里的8千万
and I would trade it all right now for a roll of Charmin.
换成一卷卫生纸
Wakey,wakey.
醒醒
- Ow! - Don't.
- 啊! - 不要
You know,you folks should be more careful.
你们应该更加小心
I hear there's all sorts of bad men out there on the road.
我听说外头有各种各样的坏人
Look,man,just take whatever you want and go.
听着 不管你们要什么 拿了赶紧走
Are you giving me orders?
你在对我发号施令吗?
Hey,take it easy,look. Side pocket.
嘿 别激动 看看侧边口袋
Oh-ho-ho! You like to have a good time? That's lucky.
你喜欢喝酒吗? 真巧
'Cause we like to have a good time too.
因为我们也喜欢喝
No! No!
不! 不!
- No! No! - Hey,leave her alone!
- 不! 不! - 嘿 放开她!
Wait your turn.
下一个轮到你
What's in the whiskey,bitch?
你在威士忌里放了什么 贱人?
So,Nate,was it? Where are you headed?
Nate 是吧? 你要去哪?
Chicago. Hoping to get on a fishing crew. You?
芝加哥 希望能搭上渔船 你呢?
- We're headed to Chicago too. - Charlie.
- 我们也要去芝加哥 - Charlie
Look,we have food,and I do kinda owe you.
听着 我们有食物 我确实也欠你个人情
Can you give us a minute?
能让我们私下谈一下吗?
Charlie,I'm telling you,you can't trust anyone.
Charlie 我告诉你 我们不能相信任何人
Is that why you carry poison whiskey?
所以你带了有毒的威士忌?
They can't all be monsters. Some people have to be all right. Don't they?
他们不可能全是坏人 有些人还是可以的 不是吗?
Up,up,up,up.
起来 起来
Let's just keep moving,all right.
继续走 好了
What's wrong?
怎么了?
I know this place. It used to be a hotel.
我知道这个地方 以前是个酒店
You stayed here?
你住过这里?
I got married here.
我在这结的婚
- Hey,blondie. - Hey,little girl.
- 嘿 金发妞 - 嘿 小姑娘
Come on over,talk to me. Come here,come here.
过来跟我聊聊 过来 快过来
Where you going?
你要去哪?
Excuse me.
打扰下
Maybe you can help me.
也许你能帮我
Oh,God,I hope so.
天哪 我也希望能帮你
- We're looking for somebody. - And that accent.
- 我们在找人 - 口音真迷人
Lady,you are classing up the joint.
小姐 你让小店蓬荜生辉啊
That shouldn't be too difficult,should it?
应该不算太难吧?
His name is Miles Matheson.
他叫Miles Matheson
Never heard of him.
从没听说过
No,he has to be here.
不 他肯定在这
What do you want me to say,kid?
你想让我说什么呢 孩子?
If you know him or if you know anyone that does,can you--
如果你认识他 或知道谁认识他 你能否...
can you please let him know that his brother's dead?
转告他 他的哥哥死了?
He was murdered by Militia.
他被军权团杀了
Who are you?
你是谁?
Charlie. Charlotte,I'm-- I'm his niece.
Charlie  Charlotte 我是... 我是他侄女
Okay. Just you,come with me.
好吧 就你 跟我来
Whoa,hey,buddy.
嘿 哥们
You're not taking her anywhere.
你哪也别想带她去
She's my niece. I don't know you.
她是我侄女 而我不认识你
- Come on. - Wait.
- 走吧 - 等等
You're Uncle Miles?
你就是Miles叔叔?
Underwhelmed?
失望了?
No,I just-- I mean,I didn't expect--
不 我只是-- 我是说 我没想到--
Come on. Not in here.
走吧 别在这说了
No funny business now.
这事儿可不好玩
No,ma'am. I'm not--
不 女士 我不--
What happened?
怎么了?
Well,if you're gonna have an asthma attack,
要是你再犯哮喘
at least you had the good sense to have it near me.
至少你可以在我旁边犯病
Here.
给
What is this?
这是什么?
You breathe it in.
你吸这个
It stops the attack before it starts.
能预防你犯哮喘
You're a doctor?
你是医生?
It was my son's.
是我儿子以前用的
Now you wanna explain this?
现在你想解释一下手铐吗?
I was running away from some soldiers.
我是从一群士兵那逃出来的
- Monroe's boys? - Yes.
- Monroe的手下? - 对
Did they follow you here?
他们跟你到这来了吗?
Look,look,I don't mean to put you to any more trouble,
我不是有意给你找麻烦的
and I owe you already,so--
而我已经欠你一份人情了 所以...
so I'll just--
所以我会...
I'll go.
我会离开
That's it.
就这样
He said to come find you and that you'd help us,and,uh...
他说让我们来找你 你能帮助我们...
and then he...
然后他就...
Yeah. I'm sorry.
我很遗憾
I wish I could've...
我希望我能...
Why did Monroe want my dad?
Monroe找我爸爸干嘛?
And why does he want you?
他找你又是为什么?
Monroe thinks your dad knew something. Something important.
Monroe认为你爸爸知道一些事情 一些重要的事情
And he thinks your dad told me,so I must know it too.
他还认为你爸爸也告诉过我 所以我一定也知道
What?
知道什么?
Why the lights went out.
知道为何电力消失了
Maybe how to turn 'em back on.
也许还有使之恢复的办法
If Monroe got the power going,that would mean tanks and planes,factories.
如果Monroe能恢复电力 他便可以拥有坦克 飞机 工厂
He'd steamroll the entire continent,and he'd butcher the other republics.
他就能席卷整块大陆 他就能灭掉其它共和国
Okay. So what do we do now?
好吧 那么现在我们怎么办?
What do we do now about what?
什么现在我们怎么办?
How are we gonna get Danny back?
我们怎么把Danny救回来?
I didn't say I was going with you.
我又没说过要跟你们一起去
What?
什么?
In case you haven't noticed,
你可能没注意到
I'm trying to maintain a certain low profile here.
我在这里努力想保持低调
No,look,look,I'm begging you.
不 我求求你了
Your brother is bait.
你弟弟是个诱饵
You understand that? I go after it,not good for him... or for me.
你明白吗? 我要是去找他 对他没有好处... 对我也没有
I,for one,would like to keep my insides on the inside.
我宁愿不出人头地
No,no,look,I have--
不 不 我...
I have lost everyone that I care about.
我已经失去了所有我关心的人
My mom is dead. My dad is dead.
我妈妈死了 我爸爸也死了
And God knows what they're doing to Danny right now.
而天知道他们正在怎么虐待Danny
So you are gonna help me get him back.
所以你必须帮我救他回来
Why's that?
凭什么?
Because we're family.
因为我们是一家人
Family?
一家人?
Kid,I don't even know you.
孩子 我甚至都不认识你
Yeah,you're right.
是的 你说得对
It was stupid of me to ask. Sorry to bother you.
我居然蠢到提出这种要求 抱歉打扰你了
What's wrong?
怎么了?
- Let's get outta here. - Charlie,what's wrong?
- 我们走吧 - Charlie 出什么事了?
- Nothing,let's go. - Tell me.
- 没什么 我们走吧 - 跟我说说
Hey,hey,hey,what happened?
嘿 嘿 嘿 怎么回事?
Nothing,let's just go.
没什么 我们快走吧
Let's just go.
快走吧
Hey,hold on.
嘿 慢着
Step back.
退后
So what'd you say to her,huh?
你跟她说了什么?
Militia,huh? When'd you enlist?
军权团? 你什么时候加入的?
Uncle Miles,this is my fault. I'm--I'm so sorry.
Miles叔叔 这是我的错 我很抱歉
He's probably from the same unit that took your brother.
他可能跟抓走你弟弟的人是一伙的
Been following you from the get-go,hoping you'd flush me out,
可能从一开始就跟着你 希望你能把我引出来
which is exactly what you did,isn't it?
你真把我引出来了 对吧?
So what are you gonna do?
你打算怎么办?
This,as far as I know,
这瓶东西 据我所知
is the last bottle of single malt in Chicago.
是芝加哥最后一瓶单一麦芽威士忌
My plan is to sit here and drink it.
我打算坐在这里喝掉它
You can't just stay here. It's not safe.
你不能坐以待毙 这儿不安全
Whose fault is that? Your boyfriend.
怪谁呢? 你的男朋友
He's gonna go and get the nearest squad.
他会找来最近的军权队
Two maybe three hours tops is what you got.
或许两个小时就到了 最多三个小时
So if I were you guys,I'd hit the road.
如果我是你们的话 现在就上路了
This is crazy. Just come with us.
你这样太疯狂了 跟我们一起走
Or don't,that's fine. But go somewhere.
不跟我们一起也没关系 但离开这儿
You can't just sit here and die.
你不能在这坐以待毙
Just go.
走吧
Uncle Miles,come on.
Miles叔叔 拜托
I said go.
说了让你们走
Get out! Get outta here!
滚! 快滚!
Good morning. May I help you?
早上好 有什么事吗?
Sorry to bother you,but we're looking for a dangerous,young fugitive.
抱歉打扰 我们在找一名危险的年轻逃犯
19,six-feet,brown hair.
19岁 一米八三 棕色头发
You're the first person I've seen in weeks.
你是我这几个礼拜见到的第一个人
What did you do before the blackout?
电力消失之前你是干什么的?
Sorry?
什么?
Just curious.
好奇而已
Humor me,please.
说来听听
I taught algebra.
我是代数老师
Me,I was an insurance adjuster.
我是保险理算员
Most of my job was figuring out
我的主要工作就是分辨
whether the things people said lined up with the truth.
人们是否在说谎
Lucky for me,it's a skill that never goes out of style.
幸运的是 这种本领永远不会过时
So take,for example,those tracks that lead right to your back door.
说说直通你家后门的脚印吧
Tracks?
脚印?
Fresh ones. About a day old. Two people.
新鲜脚印 大概是一天前留下的 两个人
A woman,who would have to be you,dragging in a man,
一个女人 应该是你 把一个男人拖了进来
and yet you say that I'm the first person you've seen in weeks.
你却说我是你这几个礼拜见到的第一个人
So tell me,does that sound like the truth to you?
你说 这听上去像真的吗?
He's gotta be long gone.
他肯定早就跑了
If he's here,Monroe wants him alive.
要是还在 Monroe想留活口
Come on down. We don't wanna hurt you.
下来吧 我们不想伤害你
I don't wanna hurt them. But I'm not going back.
我也不想伤害他们 但我不会回去的
You know,you could just let me go. I'll drink myself to death.
你们可以放过我的 我自己会喝到死
You know we can't do that.
你知道这是不可能的
I know.
我知道
Take him. Now!
抓住他 快!
Shoot him!
开枪打他!
Charlie?
Charlie?
You okay?
你没事吧?
You know,I didn't ask you to come back.
我没让你们回来
Don't look at me. I wanted to let you rot.
别看我 我很乐意让你自生自灭
Why didn't you?
为什么你不肯呢?
Because we're family,and that's what my dad would have wanted.
因为我们是一家人 我爸爸也是这样想的
Kid,if I'm coming with you,you're gonna have to dial it back a notch.
孩子 如果我和你们一起走 你要慢慢来 别太急于求成
You're coming?
你要跟我们一起走?
Loverboy will just send more troops.
你的小情人会派更多军队过来
I can't stay here.
我不能再待在这
Thank you.
谢谢
You're welcome.
不客气
We're all gonna end up with our heads on a stick,but you're welcome.
最后我们都会死 不用客气
Bass,what the hell is going on?
Bass 到底怎么回事?
I don't know,but we should get back to base.
我不知道 我们应该回基地了
This is not good.
看上去不妙
Halt right there,gentlemen. I.D.'s?
站住 先生们 身份证?
Sergeant Miles Matheson.
Miles Matheson中士
You're good.
进去吧
I-I don't-- Well,he knows me.
我没有 但他认识我
Sergeant Sebastian Monroe.
我是Sebastian Monroe中士
You're good.
进去吧
Miles.
Miles
General Monroe.
Monroe将军
Gerneral Monroe,Ben Matheson is dead. We have his son.
Monroe将军 Ben Matheson死了 我们抓到了他儿子
With respect Capt. Nevilie
此致 Nevilie上尉
The Militia was here.
军权团来过了
Did they find it?
他们发现了吗?
No
没有
So... What now?
现在怎么办?
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
--------------------------- 本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用 禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负 ---------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET- ÑÅ±´
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 小力水手 黑米 茶泡饭 Sleeper ts 校对: 尉迟逸 时间轴: 雅贝
REVOLUTION Season 1 Episode 1
末世革命 第一季 第1集